Not enough details on title page.
No Abstract.
No Future Work section. 
No Related Work section.
Not the best way of expressing as in "quick sort is a little faster".
Introduction is poor.
Algorithms are explained, but not satisfyingly enough. Also notations are used without explaining.
Experimental setup is properly done(besinde having pieces of code).
Experiments are satisfying. There could have been a better approach to charts.
Refferences not properly done.

Weak Reject